Finding Aid for the American Civil Liberties Union of Southern California Records LSC.0900
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Archive, 1974-1976
  - Reid, Joseph - Blackmail. (Box 231)
  - Relative Responsibility Law. (Box 231)
  - Report of Counsel -., 1973-1974. (Box 231)
  - Republican Convention - San Diego Project. (Box 231)
  - 1940 Resolution - Background & Position Papers - prior to rescinding. (Box 231)
  - Retirement Plan - ACLU. (Box 231)
  - Revolutionary Communist Youth problem. (Box 231)
  - Right_Wing Propaganda. (Box 231)
  - Ripston et al vs. Pitchess - Ramero-Little Trial - Court Procedures. (Box 231)
  - Rowe vs. Campbell Union High School - 9th Circuit Opinion. (Box 231)
  - San Fernando Valley College Teachers being fired - Young & Chislock. (Box 231)
  - Sarnoff, Irving. (Box 231)
  - SCAB - Anti_Riot Act. (Box 231)
  - Schact. (Box 231)
  - Schonfeld, Bernard. (Box 232)
  - School - Violence. (Box 232)
  - Schools - Higher Education - L.A. County & Southern California. (Box 232)
  - Senate Bill 1: Criminal Justice Reform Act of 1976. (Box 232)
  - Senate Bill 242: Harme_Greene Bill,., 1970. (Box 232)
  - Senate Bill 890: State Guidlines Revision of Education Code,., 1974. (Box 232)
  - Senabe Sub_committee on Constitutional Rights. (Box 232)
  - Sexual Behavior - ACLU Policy Statement. (Box 232)
  - Shatto Place. (Box 232)
  - Slaff letters (Eliz Gurley Flynn). (Box 232)
  - Smuff. (Box 232)
  - Sponsors - ACLU. (Box 232)
  - Sterilization. (Box 232)
  - Student Aid - Application & Eligibility limitions. (Box 232)
  - Study & Evaluation: CRLA,., 1971. (Box 232)
  - Suits against ACLU. (Box 232)
  - Supreme Court. (Box 233)
  - Supreme Court - Communist Party, etc. (Box 233)
  - Supreme Court Justices. (Box 233)
  - Surveillance. (Box 233)
  - Surveillance Docket National Policy., 1973 - 1976. (Box 233)
  - Surveillance - Electronic - Schwartz Report. (Box 233)
  - Survey on ACLU. (Box 233)
  - Surveys on ACLU - Scoble & Cadiz. (Box 233)
  - Survey - UCLA Research. (Box 233)
  - Sutherland, Shirley - Deportation Proceedings. (Box 233)
  - Tackwood - Police informer. (Box 233)
  - Telegrams. (Box 233)
  - Tinker Decision. (Box 233)
  - Traffic Violations Study - Judicial Council of California. (Box 233)
  - Union Agreement (ACLU & Commun. and Soc. Agency Employees Union). (Box 233)
  - United Farm Workers. (Box 233)
  - United States Commission on Civil Rights - Enforcements. (Box 233)
  - U.S.A. vs. Kinsilla, Fedrizzi, Zepeda - Police killing of Mexican-American. (Box 233)
  - Nationals. (Box 233)
  - UCLA - School of Social Welfare - Admissions Policy. (Box 233)
  - Urine Tests. (Box 233)
  - Van Hong, Hugh. (Box 233)
  - Vaughn, Daniel. (Box 233)
  - Vietnam articles. (Box 234)
  - Vietnam: Committee on Treaty & Impeachment. (Box 234)
  - Vietnam: Miscellaneous End the War Campaigns. (Box 234)
  - Vietnam Policy. (Box 234)
  - Vietnamese Students Deportation Hearings. (Box 234)
  - Violence - Center for Study, UCLA. (Box 234)
  - Violence - Center for Study, UCLA - Plan of Program. (Box 234)
  - Violence - Center for Study, UCLA - Proposed Projects. (Box 234)
  - Violence - Center for Study, UCLA - Proposed Projects. (Box 235)
  - Violence - Cneter for Study, UCLA - Review Committee Reports. (Box 235)
  - Warriner, E. (Court of Appeals Decision -., May 1973) (Box 235)
  - Watergate. (Box 235)
  - Waxman - TRO against mailing of campaign literature. (Box 235)
  - Welfare. (Box 235)
  - Welfare - Guaranteed Income. (Box 235)
  - Welfare Committee - Health Care Statement. (Box 235)
  - Welfare Proposal - Agran. (Box 235)
  - Welfare - Social. (Box 235)
  - Wells Fargo - Loan. (Box 235)
  - Wenzel. (Box 235)
  - Wire_tapping. (Box 235)
  - Witness. (Box 235)
  - Women's Rights Docket. (Box 236)
  - Women's Rights Project. (Box 236)
  - Work_Study Prpgrams - Regulations. (Box 236)
  - Miscellaneous Local Chapters [Collected by UCLA]. (Box 236)
- Archive, 1976-1980
  The following records were deposited in 1980. As in previous entries, some of the material covers earlier dates. Boxes 237-294: USA vs. Anthony Joseph Russo, Jr. and Daniel Ellsberg.
  - Court Transcripts. volumes 1-8,., June 5, 1972-June 26, 1972. (Box 237)
  - ___ ____. volumes 9-15, (volumes 12 & 13 are lacking)., June 27, 1972-July 1, 1972. (Box 238)
  - ___ ____. volumes 16-19,., July 10-13, 1972. (Box 239)
  - ___ ____. volumes 20-23,., July 15-19, 1972. (Box 240)
  - ___ ____. volumes 24-28,., July 20-25, 1972. (Box 241)
  - ___ ____. volumes 28-40,., July 26-Dec 14, 1972. (Box 242)
  - ___ ____. volumes 41-45,., Dec 20, 1972-Jan 8, 1973. (Box 243)
  - ___ ____. volumes 46-49,., Jan 9-12, 1973. (Box 244)
  - ___ ____. volumes 50-53,., Jan 15-18, 1973. (Box 245)
  - ___ ____. volumes 54-57,., Jan 19-24, 1973. (Box 246)
  - ___ ____. volumes 58-62,., Jan 26-Feb 1, 1973. (Box 247)
  - ___ ____. volumes 63-67,., Feb 2-8, 1973. (Box 248)
  - ___ ____. volumes 68-72,., Feb 9-15, 1973. (Box 249)
  - ___ ____. volumes 73-77,., Feb 16-23, 1973. (Box 250)
  - ___ ____. volumes 78-83,., Feb 26-Mar 5, 1973. (Box 251)
  - ___ ____. volumes 84-88,., Mar 6-12, 1973. (Box 252)
  - ___ ____. volumes 89-94,., Mar 13-20, 1973. (Box 253)
  - ___ ____. volumes 95-99,., Mar 21-28, 1973. (Box 254)
  - ___ ____. volumes 100-104,., Mar 29-Apr 4, 1973. (Box 255)
  - ___ ____. volumes 105-109,., Apr 5-11, 1973. (Box 256)
  - ___ ____. volumes 110-116,., Apr 12-20, 1973. (Box 257)
  - ___ ____. volumes 117-122,., Apr 23-30, 1973. (Box 258)
  - ___ ____. volumes 124-129,., May 2-10, 1973. (Box 259)
  - Election of Jurors (Box 260)
    - Asta, Jouis J. (Box 260)
    - Gordon, Sally. (Box 260)
    - Oshita, Mitsuru. (Box 260)
    - Bahena, Dora. (Box 260)
    - Conhaim, Lurlyne. (Box 260)
    - Abata, William. (Box 260)
    - Ostgaard, Mary. (Box 260)
    - Clearwaters, Paul. (Box 260)
    - Morgan, Frances. (Box 260)
    - Wiegand, Anne. (Box 260)
    - Turnbull, Ardis. (Box 260)
    - Arneaud, Darlene. (Box 260)
    - Avalos, Eleanor. (Box 260)
    - Baltadono, Wilfred. (Box 260)
    - Boutellier, Jean. (Box 260)
    - Duhigg, Joan. (Box 260)
    - Embree, Dulcey. (Box 261)
    - Escadero, Mercedes. (Box 261)
    - Hutton, Lois. (Box 261)
    - Johnson, Mitchell. (Box 261)
    - Kaschube, Margaret. (Box 261)
    - Kelpe, Donna. (Box 261)
    - Leemon, Gary. (Box 261)
    - Legre, Gerard. (Box 261)
    - McNamara, Elizabeth. (Box 261)
    - Martinez, Patrucua. (Box 261)
    - Morris, Helen. (Box 261)
    - Muoio, June. (Box 261)
    - Neal, Cora. (Box 261)
    - Ortman, Physsis. (Box 261)
    - Pittman, Monellis. (Box 261)
    - Suanders, Annie. (Box 261)
    - Schlaba, Lola. (Box 261)
    - Vasquez, Lupe. (Box 261)
  - Los Angeles County, Office of the Registrar-Recorder: Registered voters as of Computer print-outs., April 13, 1972. (Box 262)
  - U.S.vs. Anthony Joseph Russo, Jr. and Daniel Ellsberg. Pleading Files. (Box 263)
    - Index to formal files. (Box 263)
    - Bekins warrant (Seized property). (Box 263)
    - Appendix re. Constitutionality & Construction motion. (Box 263)
    - Defendants' public statements. (Box 263)
    - Docket sheets. (Box 263)
    - Electronic Surveillance. (Box 263)
    - Electronic Surveillance-Supreme Court proceedings. (Box 263)
    - Gravel. (Box 263)
    - Indictment. (Box 263)
    - Informa Pauperis. (Box 263)
    - Jury: Grand Jury lists & disclosure of proceedings. (Box 263)
  - U.S. vs. Russo & Ellsberg. Pleading Files. (Box 264)
    - Jury: Instructions. (Box 264)
    - Exhibit lists and Witness lists. (Box 264)
    - Jury: Voir Dire; Instructions to Counsel, etc. (Box 264)
    - Lack of Authorized Signature. (Box 264)
    - Prejudicial matter. (Box 265)
    - Protective Order. (Box 265)
    - Protective Order: Reciepts & Agreements. (Box 265)
    - Rand Subpoena Duces Tecum. (Box 265)
    - Reading of Indictment. (Box 265)
    - Retaliatory Prosecution. (Box 265)
    - Selective Prosecution. (Box 265)
    - Severance. (Box 265)
    - Surplusage. (Box 266)
    - Government Subpoenas. (Box 266)
    - Mistrial. (Box 266)
    - Pro Se. (Box 266)
    - Classification markings. (Box 266)
    - Motion for Transfer of Trial. (Box 266)
    - Telephone records. (Box 266)
    - Gag Order. (Box 266)
    - Motion for Judgment of Acquittal. (Box 266)
  - Second Supplemental appendix: Government's motion Re Jury selection and instructions to Counsel (Parts 1-2). (Box 267)
  - Appendix to Government's Motion Re Jury selection and instructions to Counsel. (Parts 1-3). (Box 268)
  - Second Supplemental appendix: Government's motion Re Jury selection and instructions to Counsel (Part 3). (Box 268)
  - Defendants' Statements (Box 269)
    - Amendment of Solicitation,., June 30, 1967 (Box 269)
    - ___ ____.., Feb 1, 1968 (Box 269)
    - ___ ____.., May 21, 1968 (Box 269)
    - ___ ____. letter., Feb 1, 1969 & (Box 269)
    - ___ ____.., Feb 1, 1971 (Box 269)
    - ___ ____.., AUG 20, 1971 (Box 269)
    - ___ ____.., Oct 14, 1971 (Box 269)
    - Appendix to?(Press clippings re. Ellsberg)? Appendix A of Government montion re. Jury selection?. (Box 269)
    - Bill of Particulars. (Box 269)
    - Chief Fox Receipt:., 1/21/69 (Box 269)
    - Classification authentication form: Gurtov. (Box 269)
    - Classified Material transfer:., 5/20/70 (Box 269)
    - Communications Intelligence (Court House). (Box 269)
    - Courier Authorizations. (Box 269)
    - Letter to RAND from Assistant Secretary of Defense., dated 2/1/67 (Box 269)
    - Contract #HC15670158 with RAND: Defense Supply Service,., 2/1/67 (Box 269)
    - Letter contract #F4462067C0045. Dept. Air Force & RAND. (Box 269)
    - CPFF contract #F4460267C0045, Air Force & RAND., Sept 1, 1966. (Box 269)
    - Department of Army Letter Contract to RAND., 2/1/67 (Box 269)
    - D.O.D. Directive, #5200.1,., July 8, 1957 (Box 269)
    - D.O.D. Directive #5210.8,., Feb 15, 1962 (Box 269)
    - D.O.D. Instruction #5210.43,., Oct 22, 1963 (Box 269)
    - D.O.D. Instruction #5210.44,., Feb 17, 1964 (Box 269)
    - D.O.D. Instruction #5210.47,., Dec 31 1964 (Box 269)
    - D.O.D. form dated 2/20/69, re contract SD-200 with RAND. (Box 269)
    - Department of State Security Regulations, Sec 417--Removal of Records. (Box 269)
    - Docket Sheets. (Box 269)
    - 22 page Ellsberg Personnel Action. (Box 269)
    - File Forms. (Box 269)
    - Fingerprint cards. (Box 269)
    - 47 vol. sets: receipts., 9/69 (Box 269)
    - Incoming TS Log: Gurtov. (Box 269)
    - ___ ____: JCS. (Box 269)
    - ___ ____:, 18 vols. (Box 269)
    - Index to Annex A,., Mar 1967 (Box 269)
    - Inventories. (Box 269)
    - Justice: Protection of Defense Information. (Box 269)
    - Latent Fingerprint Chart. (Box 269)
    - OSD Administrative Instruction #8,., July 1954 (Box 269)
    - OSD (ISA) Memo of Transmittal,., 1/17/69 (Box 269)
    - Defendants' Preliminary Exhibits Lists--Extra copies. (Box 269)
    - Public Statements of Defendants. (Box 270)
    - RAND Check Sheet for Vu Van Thai. (Box 270)
    - Vu Van Thai Contract #70663 with RAND,., Oct 1 1969 (Box 270)
    - RAND Employee History Report for Ellsberg. (Box 270)
    - RAND Employee History Report for Gurtov. (Box 270)
    - Security Manual, RAND,., May 1968 (Box 270)
    - Security Manual, RAND,., July, 1970 (Box 270)
    - RAND Security Statement: Ellsberg. (Box 270)
    - RAND Security Statement: Russo. (Box 270)
    - Receipts:., 3/3/69 & 8/28/69 (Box 270)
    - Record of Access: JCS. (Box 270)
    - Records of Access:, 18 vols. (Box 270)
    - Russo: Bendix Clearance. (Box 270)
    - Selective Prosecution. (Box 270)
    - State Department Form #J-F3 Separation Statement. (Box 270)
    - State Department Form J-F4 Security Acknowledgement. (Box 270)
    - State/AID/ USIA Security Regulations (excerpts from 5 FAM 900). (Box 270)
    - Subpoenas. (Box 270)
    - TS Machine Punch Cards. (Box 270)
    - Transcript of Hearing: vol.1,., Apr 5, 1949 (Box 270)
    - Transcript of Hearing: vol. 2,., Apr 6, 1949 (Box 270)
    - Transcript of Hearing: vol. 3,., Apr 7, 1949 (Box 270)
    - Voir Dire. (Box 270)
    - Wright Commission. (Box 270)
    - Bursey vs. U.S. (Box 271)
    - Hearings on 1949 Bill. (Box 271)
    - Ellsberg--Research Affidavits re Ad Hoc Declassification Policy. (Box 271)
    - Ellsberg--Boston File. (Box 271)
    - Ellsberg--Media, Editorial Comment. (Box 271)
    - Ellsberg--Research: Clippings re Classification & Declassification (Leaks). (Box 271)
    - Ellsberg--Defense Committee. (Box 271)
    - Ellsberg--Miscellaneous Letters. (Box 271)
    - Ellsberg--Schedules. (Box 271)
    - Government's Case. (Box 271)
    - Jury Selection. (Box 271)
  - The Washington Post: Sunday 2/13-A-3 (Box 271)
    - Ahmad, Egbal. (Box 271)
    - Gravel Edition. (Box 271)
    - Chile. (Box 271)
    - Voir Dire Guidelines. (Box 271)
    - Ellsberg--Press Releases. (Box 271)
    - Ellsberg--Pentagon Papers as History. (Box 271)
    - Ellsberg--Research State Secrets and Leaks. (Box 271)
  - Transcript Index. (Box 272)
  - Defense Heine Exhibits. (Box 272)
  - Defendants' Fact Exhibits & Brady. (Box 272)
  - Government's Exhibits. (Box 272)
  - Defendants' Exhibits (Box 273)
    - Exhibits A-C. (Box 273)
    - Exhibits E-F. (Box 274)
    - Exhibit J: #1-206. (Box 275)
    - Exhibit J: #207-218. (Box 276)
    - Exhibit K: #41-91. (Box 276)
    - Exhibit K: #105-195. (Box 277)
    - Exhibits L-V. (Box 277)
    - Rejected Defendants' Exhibits A & C. (Box 277)
  - RM-5617-ISA/ARP (Part II)., July 1968 (Box 278)
  - Government's Exhibits 1-6 (Part I). (Box 278)
  - Government's Exhibits (Box 279)
    - Exhibits 6 (Part II) - 13. (Box 279)
    - Exhibits #14-18. (Box 280)
  - Materials relating to Government's Exhibits. no. 1-9. (Box 281)
  - Materials relating to Government's Exhibits. no. 10-14 (Box 282)
    (With an overview of Exhibits 15-18)
  - Materials relating to Government's Exhibits. no. 15-18. (Box 283)
  - Reporter's Transcript of Proceedings:., Tuesday, Feb 29, 1972 (Box 284)
  - ___ ____:., Wednesday, Mar 1, 1972 (Box 284)
  - ___ ____:., Tuesday, Apr 11, 1972 (Box 284)
  - ___ ____:., Tuesday, Apr 25, 1972 (Box 284)
  - ___ ____:., Tuesday, May 2, 1972 (Box 284)
  - Press Clippings., 1971 (Box 285)
  - ___ ____. Prior to., Oct 1972 (Box 285)
  - ___ ____.., Jan 1972 (Box 285)
  - ___ ____.., Feb 1972 (Box 285)
  - ___ ____.., Mar 1972 (Box 285)
  - ___ ____.., Apr 1972 (Box 285)
  - ___ ____.., May 1972 (Box 285)
  - ___ ____.., June 1972 (Box 285)
  - ___ ____.., July 1972 (Box 285)
  - ___ ____.., Aug 1972 (Box 285)
  - ___ ____.., Sept 1972 (Box 285)
  - ___ ____.., Oct/Nov/Dec 1972 (Box 285)
  - ___ ____. Before Nov 1972. (Box 285)
  - Press Clippings - Christian Science Monitor., Dec 1972: (Box 286)
  - ___ ____. Los Angeles Herald Examiner., Dec 1972: (Box 286)
  - ___ ____. Los Angeles Times., Dec 1972: (Box 286)
  - ___ ____. New York Times., Dec 1972: (Box 286)
  - ___ ____. Miscellaneous Publications., Dec 1972: (Box 286)
  - ___ ____.., Jan-Mar 1973 (Box 286)
  - ___ ____. Christian Science Monitor., Jan 1973: (Box 286)
  - ___ ____. Los Angeles Herald Examiner., Jan 1973: (Box 286)
  - ___ ____. Los Angeles Times., Jan 1973: (Box 286)
  - ___ ____. New York Times., Jan 1973: (Box 286)
  - ___ ____. New York Daily News., Jan 1973: (Box 286)
  - ___ ____. Washington Post., Jan 1973: (Box 286)
  - ___ ____. Miscellaneous Publications., Jan 1973: (Box 286)
  - ___ ____. Christian Science Monitor., Feb 1973: (Box 286)
  - ___ ____. Los Angeles Herald Examiner., Feb 1973: (Box 286)
  - ___ ____. Los Angeles Times., Feb 1973: (Box 286)
  - ___ ____. New York Daily News., Feb 1973: (Box 286)
  - ___ ____. New York Times., Feb 1973: (Box 286)
  - Press Clippings - Washington Post., Feb 1973: (Box 286)
  - ___ ____. Miscellaneous Publications., Feb 1973: (Box 286)
  - ___ ____. Christian Science Monitor., Mar 1973: (Box 286)
  - ___ ____. Los Angeles Times., Mar 1973: (Box 286)
  - ___ ____. New York Daily News., Mar 1973: (Box 286)
  - ___ ____. New York Times., Mar 1973: (Box 286)
  - ___ ____. Washinton Post., Mar 1973: (Box 286)
  - ___ ____. Miscellaneous Clippings., Mar 1973: (Box 286)
  - ___ ____.., Apr 1 - May 1, 1973 (Box 286)
  - ___ ____. Christian Science Monitor., Apr 1973: (Box 286)
  - Press Clippings - Los Angeles Herald Examiner., Apr 1973: (Box 287)
  - ___ ____. Los Angeles Times., Apr 1973: (Box 287)
  - ___ ____. New York Daily News., Apr 1973: (Box 287)
  - ___ ____. New York Times., Apr 1973: (Box 287)
  - ___ ____. Washington Post., Apr 1973: (Box 287)
  - ___ ____. Miscellaneous Publications., Apr 1973: (Box 287)
  - ___ ____.., May 1-15, 1973 (Box 287)
  - ___ ____. Christian Science Monitor., May 1973: (Box 287)
  - ___ ____. Los Angeles Times., May 1973: (Box 287)
  - ___ ____. Miscellaneous Publications., May 1973: (Box 287)
  - Pentagon Papers Project - Miscellaneous. (Box 287)
  - Cassette Tapes of Press Conferences Prior to., 1972 (Box 287)
  - Press - Background Material. (Box 287)
  - Press - Biographies (Defendants & Counsel). (Box 287)
  - Press - Biographies (Witnesses). (Box 287)
  - Press - Photos. (Box 287)
  - Press - Releases, Letters & Articles. (Box 288)
  - Press - Summary of Prosecution Case. (Box 288)
  - Press - Weekly Summaries. (Box 288)
  - Watergate - File Copies of Everything. (Box 288)
  - Hearings Files (Box 289)
    - Pentagon Papers (Gravel Edition). (Box 289)
    - Opening Statement. (Box 289)
    - Ellsberg: Trial Preparation / Defense - Nature of the War. (Box 289)
    - Research - Wiretapping. (Box 289)
    - Attorney General Reports. (Box 289)
    - Bill of Rights Foundation. (Box 289)
    - General Clippings. (Box 289)
    - Conspirary Trials: Angela Davis. (Box 289)
    - Department of Defense. (Box 289)
    - Ellsberg: Clippings. (Box 289)
    - Ellsberg - Government Response to Discovery. (Box 289)
    - Facts: Halperin Memorandum. (Box 289)
    - Facts: The War: Damage. (Box 289)
    - Juries. (Box 289)
    - Press Freedom. (Box 290)
    - Research - Miscellaneous. (Box 290)
    - Trial Subpoenas. (Box 290)
    - Basic. (Box 290)
    - Harrisburg - Clippings. (Box 290)
    - San Quentin Six. (Box 290)
    - Ellsberg - Research: Government Deceit. (Box 290)
    - Ellsberg - Research: Materials to be read. (Box 290)
    - Ellsberg - Background: Miscellaneous. (Box 290)
    - Ellsberg - Background: Newspaper Releases. (Box 290)
    - Ellsberg - Background: Personnel History. (Box 290)
    - Ellsberg - Background: Revocable Trust. (Box 290)
    - Ellsberg - Background: Writings. (Box 290)
    - Ellsberg - Background: Biographical. (Box 290)
    - Ellsberg - Background: Tony Russo. (Box 290)
    - Ellsberg - Background: Janicke. (Box 290)
    - Evidence - Ellsberg. (Box 290)
    - Miscellaneous - Ellsberg. (Box 290)
    - Ellsberg - Motion to Dismiss. (Box 291)
    - Jacobs, Paul. (Box 291)
    - New York Times: Impeachment Advertisment. (Box 291)
    - Opening Statement. (Box 291)
    - Classification LBJ Conference. (Box 291)
    - Chomsky. (Box 291)
    - Harrisburg. (Box 291)
    - Trial Memo. (Box 291)
    - Sealed Indictment Motion (Draft). (Box 291)
    - Ellsberg Lectures. (Box 291)
    - Count I Part I: Ellsberg Research Files. (Box 291)
    - Ellsberg - Conspiracy to Defraud the U.S. (Box 291)
    - The English Official Secrets Act. (Box 291)
    - Ellsberg - The Backroom Boys. (Box 291)
    - Ellsberg - N.Y.U. Talks. (Box 291)
    - Ellsberg - Violations of Treaties. (Box 291)
  - HEINE Material. (Box 292)
  - HEINE Material. (Box 293)
  - HEINE Material (Box 294)
    END OF PENTAGON PAPERS FILES
  - Impeachment (Box 295)
    - Articles. (Box 295)
    - Memos, ect. (Box 295)
    - ACLU News Releases. (Box 295)
    - Clippings. (Box 295)
    - Coordinators. (Box 295)
    - Correspondence. (Box 295)
    - The First Pamphlet Proposing the Creation of the Committee of Correspondence to Redeem the Constitution of the U.S. by Causing The Impeachment of Richard M. Nixon,., Oct 24, 1973. (Box 296)
    - Miscellaneous Memos, ect. (Box 296)
    - Correspondence. (Box 296)
    - Letters to Congressmen. (Box 296)
    - Impeachment Meeting., November 1973 (Box 296)
    - Monies. (Box 296)
    - Publications. (Box 296)
    - Speaker's Kit. (Box 296)
    - Impeachment Tally. (Box 296)
  - Watergate Exhibits. (Box 297)
  - 1970 Census Data by Zip Codes for Los Angeles and Orange Counties. (Box 297)
  - Ripston, Ramona - Newsclippings and photos. (Box 297)
  - College Mailing Lists. (Box 297)
  - Our Mind Is Our Weapon - Soladad Prison Paper. (Box 297)
  - Public Domain Material. (Box 298)
  - Memorandum of Defendant New York Times Company in Opposition to Issuance of Preliminary Injunction (A). (Box 299)
  - Possible Prosecution of New York Times Criminal - Section 794: U.S. vs. New York Times, 18 USCA 798 (B). (Box 299)
  - Criminal Analysis of Justice White's Opinion (C). (Box 299)
  - Criminal Responsibility of Corporation; Individual Criminal Liability; Fifth Amendment Privilege (D). (Box 299)
  - Historical Application of SS 793 & 794 of the Espionage Act; Memoranda Re 18 USC 793 Gorin vs. U.S. (E). (Box 299)
  - Analysis of Government's Brief Filed in Gorin Re Scope or Reach of Present Title 18 USC S793 (F). (Box 299)
  - 18 USC S2315 Analysis of 18 USC SS 2315 and 641 (G). (Box 299)
  - 18 USC S793 (E) & 18 USC S798 (H). (Box 299)
  - United States vs. Judith Coplon,., 1950 (Box 299)
  - Riverside, Calif. Police Murders. (Box 300)
  - Legislative Files:, 1974-1977 (Box 301)
    - Abortion. (Box 301)
    - ACLU 50th Anniversary: Freedom of the Press. (Box 301)
    - ACLU Docket - National - New Cases Listed., 1972-1976 (Box 301)
    - ACLU Docket., 1975-1976 (Box 301)
    - ACLU Docket and Report of Counsel., 1975-1977 (Box 301)
    - ACLU Legislative Program. (Box 301)
    - ACLU National Office Correspondence. (Box 301)
    - ACLU - Other Affiliates. (Box 301)
    - Affirmative Action. (Box 301)
    - Affirmative Action Committee. (Box 301)
    - Amnesty. (Box 301)
    - Angola. (Box 301)
    - Attorney Fees Memo., 10/17/74 (Box 301)
    - Attorney General - Opinions. (Box 301)
    - Bail Reform. (Box 302)
    - Begin. (Box 302)
    - Bell, Griffin. (Box 302)
    - Bicentennial. (Box 302)
    - Bradley, Thomas. (Box 302)
    - Brown, George Jr. (Box 302)
    - Bycel, Ben - Weekly Reports. (Box 302)
    - California Church Council (Legislative News Alert). (Box 302)
    - California Democratic Council. (Box 302)
    - Californians for Liberal Representation. (Box 302)
    - Campaign Finance Reform. (Box 302)
    - Campaign Statement of Contributions. (Box 302)
    - Capital Punishment - Execution Data,., 1969 (Box 302)
    - Capital Punishment - Execution Data,., 1970 (Box 302)
    - Capital Punishment -., 1971 (Box 302)
    - Carter, Jimmy. (Box 302)
    - Center for the Reduction of Violence (UCLA). (Box 302)
    - CIA - FBI. (Box 302)
    - City Lobbying Ordinancy. (Box 302)
    - Civil Liberties Lobby,., 1977 (Box 302)
    - Common Cause (John Gardner). (Box 303)
    - Community Relations Conference. (Box 303)
    - Congressional Liasons. (Box 303)
    - Consumer Issues. (Box 303)
    - Cranston, Senator Alan. (Box 303)
    - Criminal Code Revision U.S. S-1. (Box 303)
    - Cunningham (Councilperson). (Box 303)
    - Day in Sacramento -., 1974 (Box 303)
    - Day in Sacramento -., 1976 (Box 303)
    - Death Penalty., 1976-1977 (Box 303)
    - Deprogramming. (Box 303)
    - Development. (Box 303)
    - Districting Board of Education. (Box 304)
    - Draft Repeal. (Box 304)
    - Edelman, Ed. (Box 304)
    - Election Information. (Box 304)
    - Fair Housing. (Box 304)
    - Farm Workers. (Box 304)
    - Farm Workers Initiative - Yes on Proposition 14. (Box 304)
    - Fluoridation. (Box 304)
    - Ford, Gerald (President). (Box 304)
    - Free Press. (Box 304)
    - Friends Committee on Legislation. (Box 304)
    - Glendale Newsrack Ordinance., June 1975 (Box 304)